{
    "subject": "resource/Acharya_Ramlochan_Saran",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfDeath",
    "object": "Darbhanga Bihar, India",
    "human_readable": "Acharya Ramlochan Saran died in Darbhanga, Bihar, India.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9477059841156006,
            "question": "Was Acharya Ramlochan Saran from Darbhanga?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9345405697822571,
            "question": "Where in India did Acharya Ramlochan Saran die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8815750479698181,
            "question": "Where did Acharya Ramlochan Saran die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8542978763580322,
            "question": "What is the state where Acharya Ramlochan Saran died?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8202226161956787,
            "question": "Is Darbhanga in Bihar, India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7881264686584473,
            "question": "Can you tell me the place of death of Acharya Ramlochan Saran?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7803370952606201,
            "question": "Who is Acharya Ramlochan Saran?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7736692428588867,
            "question": "What is the full location of Acharya Ramlochan Saran's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7414750456809998,
            "question": "What country was Acharya Ramlochan Saran living in at the time of his death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5502783060073853,
            "question": "In which city did Acharya Ramlochan Saran pass away?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Acharya Ramlochan Saran died in Darbhanga, Bihar, India.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1937_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country was Acharya Ramlochan Saran living in at the time of his death?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1937_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the full location of Acharya Ramlochan Saran's death?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1937_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Acharya Ramlochan Saran?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1937_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1937_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1937_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1937_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1937_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1937_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1937_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1937_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1937_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1937_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1937_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all documents mention Acharya Ramlochan Saran as being associated with Darbhanga, Bihar, and there are multiple mentions of his death in various places within these documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provided mention that Acharya Ramlochan Saran (1889 \u20131971) was born in Darbhanga, Bihar, and died in Darbhanga in the year 1971. This supports the statement that Acharya Ramlochan Saran died in Darbhanga, Bihar, India."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}